University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Meeting Records, 1964-2018; 4; 3.75 cubic ft.; 938 Digital Files
  - 2016-2017 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2016 July-2017 June
    - 2017 0424 Senate agenda etc - Senate Agenda for April 24 Meeting.msg, 2017 April 17
    - 2017 0424 Senate agenda etc - Senate minutes GSA report - GSA Task Force Letter 3-13-17.docx, 2017 April 4
    - 2017 0424 Senate agenda etc - Senate Provost Report April 3 2017.docx, 2017 April 4
    - 2017 0508 Senate agenda etc - 161704 MS Data Sci.pdf, 2017 May 1
    - 2017 0508 Senate agenda etc - 161705 CCL Advanced Cert.pdf, 2017 May 1
    - 2017 0508 Senate agenda etc - 161706 Leadership Minor Proposal 5_8_17.pdf, 2017 May 1
    - 2017 0508 Senate agenda etc - 201617 Senate Minutes 0424jcedits chp edits.docx, 2017 May 11
    - 2017 0508 Senate agenda etc - 2017Agenda Senate 0508_jpcDraft0430.doc, 2017 May 1
    - 2017 0508 Senate agenda etc - Council and Committee Reports May 8 Senate revised chp 315pm.docx, 2017 May 1
    - 2017 0508 Senate agenda etc - FAR report to Senate 2017.pptx, 2017 June 8
    - 2017 0508 Senate agenda etc - Senate Agenda for May 8 Meeting.msg, 2017 May 1
  - 2015-2016 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2015 July-2016 June
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0125 Agenda and related materials - 012516 SEC COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2016 January 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0125 Agenda and related materials - 1516-03 TESOL Online Grad Cert Proposal.pdf, 2016 January 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0125 Agenda and related materials - 1516-03A CARE.pdf, 2016 January 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0125 Agenda and related materials - 2015-16 SECMinutes1130caf.docx, 2016 January 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0125 Agenda and related materials - 2015-16 SECMinutes1209caf.docx, 2016 January 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0125 Agenda and related materials - 2016-CAREGuidelinesandProcedures011516.pdf, 2016 January 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0125 Agenda and related materials - SEC Agenda 01252016.msg, 2016 January 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0125 Agenda and related materials - SEC_Agenda_012516.docx, 2016 January 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0208 Agenda and related materials - 020816 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2016 February 2
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0208 Agenda and related materials - 2015-16 Senate Minutes 1207 caf.doc, 2016 February 23
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0208 Agenda and related materials - 2015AgendaSenate020616 update.doc, 2016 February 2
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0208 Agenda and related materials - Senate Agenda for February 8th.msg, 2016 February 2
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0208 Agenda and related materials - ~$15AgendaSenate020616 update.doc, 2016 February 23
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0307 Agenda and related materials - 030716 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2016 February 29
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0307 Agenda and related materials - 2015-16 Senate Minutes 0208 caf.doc, 2016 February 29
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0307 Agenda and related materials - 2015AgendaSenate030716.doc, 2016 February 29
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0307 Agenda and related materials - 2016Senate Meeting03-07-caf.pptx, 2016 March 7
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0307 Agenda and related materials - For today's meeting.msg, 2016 March 7
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0307 Agenda and related materials - Senate Agenda for March 7th.msg, 2016 February 29
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0404 Agenda and related materials - 040416 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2016 March 28
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0404 Agenda and related materials - 2015 Faculty Meeting Minutes 1027.doc, 2016 April 8
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0404 Agenda and related materials - 2015-16 Senate Minutes 0307.doc, 2016 March 28
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0404 Agenda and related materials - 201516AgendaSenate040416.doc, 2016 March 28
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0404 Agenda and related materials - Applied Learning for Senate.pptx, 2016 April 4
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0404 Agenda and related materials - Emeritus Resolution 022916.pdf, 2016 March 28
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0404 Agenda and related materials - FAR report to Senate 2016.pptx, 2016 April 12
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0404 Agenda and related materials - Senate Agenda for April 4th.msg, 2016 March 28
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0425 Agenda and related materials - 042516 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.DOCX, 2016 April 18
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0425 Agenda and related materials - 151604 CEHC BA BS PROPOSAL Apr 7 2016.pdf, 2016 April 18
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0425 Agenda and related materials - 201516 Senate Minutes 0307fox.doc, 2016 April 18
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0425 Agenda and related materials - 201516 Senate Minutes 0404 fox final.doc, 2016 April 28
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0425 Agenda and related materials - Senate agenda 042516.docx, 2016 April 18
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0425 Agenda and related materials - Senate Agenda for April 25th.msg, 2016 April 18
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0425 Agenda and related materials - Vice-Chair and Secretary Election message.msg, 2016 April 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0425 Agenda and related materials - ~$1516 Senate Minutes 0404 fox final.doc, 2016 April 28
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - 050916 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.DOCX, 2016 May 2
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - 151603A Clarification of CAA Responsibilities.pdf, 2016 May 2
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - 151605 Amend Policy re Cert in FT Grad Enrlmt.pdf, 2016 May 2
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - 201516 Senate Minutes 0425 Fox.doc, 2016 July 13
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - Senate agenda 050916.docx, 2016 May 2
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - Senate Agenda for May 9th.msg, 2016 May 2
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - 151606 - 151606 Grad Cert in Computing Ed w DE supplement.pdf, 2016 May 11
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - 151606 - 151606 drafts - 151606 Grad Cert in Computing Ed.pdf, 2016 May 2
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - 151606 - 151606 drafts - Distance-Education-Format-Proposal- CCE.DOC, 2016 May 11
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0509 Agenda and related materials - 151606 - 151606 drafts - Distance-Education-Format-Proposal- CCE.pdf, 2016 May 11
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0928 Agenda and related materials - 092815 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2015 September 22
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0928 Agenda and related materials - 151601A Amendment Assymetry in LISC Standing Committees.docx, 2015 September 22
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0928 Agenda and related materials - 151602A to update Section X4 GAC (1).docx, 2015 September 22
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0928 Agenda and related materials - 2015 Senate Minutes 0511.doc, 2015 September 22
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0928 Agenda and related materials - 2015-928Powerpoint Slides-caf final.pptx, 2015 September 28
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0928 Agenda and related materials - 201516 Senate Meeting Schedule.pdf, 2015 September 22
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0928 Agenda and related materials - 2015AgendaSenate928 final.doc, 2015 September 22
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 0928 Agenda and related materials - Senate Agenda for September 28th.msg, 2015 September 22
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1019 Agenda and related materials - 101915 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.DOCX, 2015 October 13
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1019 Agenda and related materials - 1516-01A Charter Amendment Assymetry in LISC Standing Committees.docx, 2015 October 13
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1019 Agenda and related materials - 1516-02A Charter Amendment to update Section X.4 (GAC).docx, 2015 October 13
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1019 Agenda and related materials - 2015-1019.pptx, 2015 October 19
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1019 Agenda and related materials - 2015-16 Senate Minutes 0928 Fox.doc, 2015 November 6
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1019 Agenda and related materials - 2015AgendaSenate1019.doc, 2015 October 13
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1019 Agenda and related materials - Deactivation of PR Studies Motion.pdf, 2015 October 13
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1019 Agenda and related materials - Senate Agenda for October 19th.msg, 2015 October 13
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1116 Agenda and related materials - 2015-1116 final caf.pptx, 2015 November 24
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1116 Agenda and related materials - 2015-16 Senate Minutes 1019.doc, 2015 November 16
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1116 Agenda and related materials - Senate Agenda for November 16th.msg, 2015 November 9
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1207 Agenda and related materials - 1207 15 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2015 December 1
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1207 Agenda and related materials - 2015-16 Senate Minutes 1116 Fox.doc, 2016 January 11
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1207 Agenda and related materials - 2015AgendaSenate1207.doc, 2015 December 1
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1207 Agenda and related materials - 2015SENATE12-07-15.pptx, 2015 December 7
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1207 Agenda and related materials - Contingent_Faculty_Committee_Report_10-1-2015 (1).pdf, 2015 December 1
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1207 Agenda and related materials - contingent_report uup.pdf, 2015 December 1
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1207 Agenda and related materials - Report_of_the_Graduate_Stipend_Committee_final_draft_070615.pdf, 2015 December 1
    - 2015-16 Agendas etc - 2015-16 1207 Agenda and related materials - Senate Agenda for December 7th.msg, 2015 December 1
  - 2014-2015 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2014 July-2015 June
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0209 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 02 09 15 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2015 February 2
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0209 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 1415-02 BS in Computer Engineering proposal.pdf, 2015 February 2
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0209 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2015SenateAgenda0209.doc, 2015 February 2
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0309 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 03 09 15 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2015 March 3
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0309 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Bylaw Amendment Ex-officio voting final.docx, 2015 March 3
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0309 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Bylaw Amendment Ex-officio voting final.pdf, 2015 March 10
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0309 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Senate Minutes0209.docx, 2015 March 3
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0309 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Senate Minutes1208.docx, 2015 March 3
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0309 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2015SenateAgenda0309.doc, 2015 March 3
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0309 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Senate Minutes0209.docx, 2015 March 3
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0406 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 04 06 15 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2015 March 31
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0406 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 141503 Grad Cert EP HS CS 0406.pdf, 2015 March 31
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0406 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 141504 Deactivate PR Studies Major 0323.pdf, 2015 March 31
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0406 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2015Senate Minutes0309jsm.docx, 2015 April 14
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0406 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2015Senate Minutes0309jsm_rev0406.docx, 2015 April 14
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0406 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2015SenateAgenda0406.doc, 2015 April 15
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0427 Senate Agenda and Related materials - 042715 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2015 April 21
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0427 Senate Agenda and Related materials - 141502A Charter Amendment Ex-officio voting 0427.pdf, 2015 April 21
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0427 Senate Agenda and Related materials - 141505 Discontinue Geology Grad 0427.pdf, 2015 April 21
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0427 Senate Agenda and Related materials - 2015Charter Amendment final april 19.docx, 2015 April 20
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0427 Senate Agenda and Related materials - 2015Senate Minutes0406-jsm caf.docx, 2015 April 21
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0427 Senate Agenda and Related materials - 2015SenateAgenda0427.doc, 2015 April 21
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0427 Senate Agenda and Related materials - Discontinue Geology Grad 4-2015 Bill Cover.docx.doc, 2015 April 20
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0427 Senate Agenda and Related materials - Discontinue UAlbany Geology Grad Programs 4-2015.docx, 2015 April 20
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0427 Senate Agenda and Related materials - FW SEC message to be sent.msg, 2015 April 20
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 1415-09 Bill BS Human Development.PDF, 2015 May 6
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 141501R ResolutionSupport EPHSC 0504.docx, 2015 May 6
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 141501R ResolutionSupport EPHSC 0504.pdf, 2015 May 6
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 141502A Charter Amendment Ex-officio voting.docx, 2015 May 5
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 141502A Charter Amendment Ex-officio voting.pdf, 2015 May 5
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 141507 Bill Adv Grad Cert Adolescent Special Ed.pdf, 2015 May 6
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 141508 EPHSC Minor.pdf, 2015 May 6
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 2014Senate Minutes0427 jsm.docx, 2015 May 6
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 2015 0511 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2015 May 6
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 2015 0511_Senate Council Roster for 2015 2016.xlsx, 2015 May 7
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0511 Senate Agenda and Related Items - 2015SenateAgenda0511 jsm.doc, 2015 May 6
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0929 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 1415 01A Amend re Comm on Assmt of Gov and Cons.docx, 2014 September 23
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0929 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 141501AAmendreCommAssmtGovandCons.pdf, 2014 September 23
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0929 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 201415SenateCouncilRosters0929.xls, 2014 September 29
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0929 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 201415SenateSchedule.docx, 2014 July 14
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0929 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES0929.docx, 2014 September 26
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0929 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Senate Minutes0512.docx, 2014 September 23
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 0929 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014SenateAgenda0929.doc, 2014 September 23
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1020 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014-Senate1020-jsm.pptx, 2014 October 17
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1020 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES1020.docx, 2014 October 14
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1020 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Senate Minutes0929.docx, 2014 October 14
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1020 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014SenateAgenda1020.doc, 2014 October 14
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1020 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - INTERIM PROVOST REPORT_141020_RTMedits.docx, 2014 November 4
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1117 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014 1117 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2014 November 10
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1117 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Senate Minutes0929.docx, 2014 November 4
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1117 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Senate Minutes1020.docx, 2014 November 10
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1117 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014SenateAgenda1117.doc, 2014 November 10
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1117 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014SenateMeeting1117-jsm.pptx, 2014 November 17
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1117 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014SenatePresReport0929.docx, 2014 November 4
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1117 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - Wages and Benefits Presentation.pptx, 2014 November 10
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1208 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014 1208 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.DOCX, 2015 January 26
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1208 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014Senate Minutes1117.docx, 2015 January 26
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1208 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - 2014SenateAgenda1208.doc, 2015 January 26
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2014-15 1208 Senate Agenda and Related Materials - Bill 1415-01 Grad ASECT.PDF, 2015 January 26
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 11 16 15 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2015 November 9
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 1516-01 MS in Counseling Psychology.pdf, 2015 November 9
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 1516-02 BAMA English_Liberal Studies.pdf, 2015 November 9
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2015-16 Senate Minutes 1019.doc, 2015 November 9
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - 2015AgendaSenate1116.doc, 2015 November 9
    - 2014-15 Senate Agendas and Related Materials - Senate Agenda for November 16th.msg, 2015 November 9
  - 2013-2014 Academic Year Senate Meeting Records, 2013 July-2014 June
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 10-21 - 10-21-13.doc, 2013 October 11
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 10-21 - 10.21.13 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2013 October 23
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 10-21 - Minutes 9-30-13.doc, 2013 October 11
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 11-18 - 11.18.13 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2013 November 12
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 12-9 - 12-9-13 Agenda.doc, 2013 December 3
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 12-9 - 12.09.13 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.DOCX, 2013 December 5
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 12-9 - 1314-01 Create BS Degree in Informatics.pdf, 2013 December 5
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 12-9 - 1314-02 Digital Forensics Major-FINAL12-2-13.pdf, 2013 December 5
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 12-9 - Minutes 11-18-13 Rev.doc, 2013 December 5
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 12-9 - Senate Minutes 12-9-13 - Senate Minutes 12-9-13.docx, 2014 February 4
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 9-30 - 09.30.13 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2013 September 24
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 9-30 - 1314-01A Dissolution of CAFFECoR.docx, 2013 September 10
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 9-30 - 5-13-13 Minutes.doc, 2013 September 23
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 9-30 - 9-30-13.doc, 2013 September 23
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 9-30 - Andrew Howard Resume.pdf, 2013 September 23
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 9-30 - CAFFECoR report complete.pdf, 2013 September 23
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013 Agendas - 9-30 - Copy of FINAL 2013-14 Councils and Committees Roster 5-9-13 - Changes approved 05-13-13.xlsx, 2013 September 23
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013-14 Council Reports - 09.30.13 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2013 October 4
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013-14 Council Reports - 11.18.13 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2013 November 21
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2013-14 Council Reports - 12 09 13 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2013 December 5
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2014 Agendas - 2-10 - 02 10 14 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2014 March 3
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2014 Agendas - 2-10 - 2-10-14 Agenda.doc, 2014 February 4
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2014 Agendas - 2-10 - Senate Minutes 12-9-13.docx, 2014 March 3
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2014 Agendas - 3-10 - 03 10 14 SENATE COUNCIL AND COMMITTEE SUMMARIES.docx, 2014 March 3
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2014 Agendas - 3-10 - 3-10-14 Agenda.doc, 2014 March 3
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2014 Agendas - 3-10 - Amendment 1314-02A CPCA Composition.pdf, 2014 March 3
    - 2013-14 Agendas and Related Materials - 2014 Agendas - 3-10 - Bill 1314-03 Masters in International Affairs.pdf, 2014 March 3